A Guide to the Headquarters Papers of Brigadier-General John Forbes Relating to the Expedition against Fort Duquesne in 1758
Special Collections, University of Virginia Library
- William West. "Invoice of Sundry Goods sent to Capt. Bosomworth p order of General Forbes p Robert Keech 's Waggon." Docketed: "Indian Goods sent from Mr West to Bosomworth", 1758 May 25; MsS, 2 p. (Box Box 4)
- Philadelphia, [Forbes] to St. Clair. Docketed: "Copy Letter to Sir Jno. St. Clair Phi: May 25th", 1758 May 25; L (copy), 4 p. (Box Box 4)
- Philadelphia, William Masters, John Mifflin, et al., to Forbes. Docketed: "Provinciale Commissns Philad: May 26th", 1758 May 26; LS, 2 p. (Box Box 4)
- Winchester, St. Clair to John Forbes. Docketed: "L: Sir Jno St Clair Winchester May 26th", 1758 May 26; LS, 2 p. (Box Box 4)
- Philadelphia, Forbes to the Provincial Commissioners. Docketed: "Copy Letter to the Provin: Commissrs May 27th", 1758 May 27; ALS (draft), 2 p. (Box Box 4)
- Carlisle, Draper S. Wood to Francis Hal-kett. Docketed: "Comissary Wood Carlisle May 27", 1758 May 27; ALS, 2 p. (Box Box 4)
- Carlisle, Draper S. Wood to Forbes. "A Return of Provisions in Store at Carlyle belonging to the Contractors May the 27, 1758" Docket: "Return of provisions at Carlisle. May 27th", 1758 May 27; Ms, 2 p. (Box Box 4)
- Winchester, St. Clair to [ Draper S. Wood ?] Docketed: "Letter Sir John St. Clair Winchester 27th May", 1758 May 27; L (copy), 2 p. (Box Box 4)
- Philadelphia, Forbes to Bouquet. Docketed: "Copy Letter to Col: Bouquet Philad: May 29th", [1758] May 29; L (copy), 4 p. (Box Box 4)
- Winchester, Byrd to [Forbes]. Docketed: "Col: Byrd Winchester May 29th V: Regt 926", 1758 May 29; ALS, 4 p. (Box Box 4)
- Lancaster, Adam Hoops to [Forbes]. Docketed: "Letter Mr. Hoops Lancaster 29th May", 1758 May 29; LS, 2 p. (Box Box 4)
- Winchester, St. Clair to Forbes. Docketed: "Sir John St. Clair Winchester. May 30th", 1758 May 30; LS, 3 p. (Box Box 4)
- Philadelphia, Forbes to St. Clair. Docketed: "Copy Letter to Sir Jno St. Clair Philad: May 30th", [1758] May 30; L (copy), 4 p. (Box Box 4)
- St. Clair to John Blair. Docketed: "Copy of Sr. John St Clairs Letter to Mr. Prest. Blair the 31st of May 1758", 1758 May 31; L (copy), 4 p. (Box Box 4)
- Philadelphia, Forbes to John Blair. Docketed: "Copy Letter to Mr President Blair Philad: May 31st", [1758] May 31; L, 3 p. (Box Box 4)
- Mr. Darnalls near Frederick Town, Sharpe to St Clair. Docketed: "Govr. Sharpes Lettr. to Sr Jno St. Clair of the 31st. of May 1758", 1758 May 31; LS, 2 p. (Box Box 4)
- William West. " William Speare and William Galbreath recomended to General Forbes by Wm. West for a Licence to travel with the Army....", 1758 June; MsS, 1 p. (Box Box 4)
- Fort Frederick, Dr. David Ross to Mr. Ridout. Docketed: "(Commissary of Ft. Cumberland) Extract from Mr Ross's Letter concerning the Want of Provisions at Fort Cumberland ", 1758 June 1; L (copy), 2 p. (Box Box 4)
- Joshua Howell to [Forbes]. Docketed: "Letter Josh. Howell 1st June", [1758] June 1; ALS, 2 p. (Box Box 4)
- "A Calculation of the Pay that was due to the Maryland Troops the 8th of April 1758 & of the Expence of victualling them from the 8th of Oct. to yt time." Docketed: "Calculation of Pay due to the Maryland forces & for their provisions June 1st. 1758", 1758 June 1; Ms, 3 p. (Box Box 4)
- Carlisle, Forbes to Bosomworth. Docketed: "Instructions to Capn. Bosomworth June the first 1758", 1758 June 1; L (copy), 3 p. (Box Box 4)
- Carlisle, Bosomworth to Forbes. Docketed: "Capt. Bosomworth Carlisle June 1st", 1758 June 1; ALS, 4 p. (Box Box 4)
- Carlisle, Francis West and William Bu-chanan to Bouquet, Carlisle. Docketed: "Letter Mr. West and Mr. Buchannan to Colo. Bouquet Carlisle 3rd June 1758", 1758 June 3; ALS, 2 p. (Box Box 4)
- Winchester, Byrd to [Forbes]. Docket: "Col: Byrd Winchester June 3d ", 1758 June 3; ALS, 4 p. (Box Box 4)
- Carlisle, Draper S. Wood to Bouquet. Docketed: "Representation of the King's Comissary", 1758 June 3; ALS, 3 p. (Box Box 4)
- Williamsburg, John Blair to St. Clair. Docketed: "Presidt Blair to Sir John St. Clair Williamsbg June 3d", 1758 June 3; ALS, 4 p. (Box Box 4)
- Winchester, St. Clair to Forbes. Docketed: "Sir John St Clair Winchester June 3d", 1758 June 3; ALS, 4 p. (Box Box 4)
- Albany, Abercromby to Forbes. Docketed: "Genll Abercromby Albany June 4th Recd. 10th", 1758 June 4; LS, 5 p. (Box Box 4)
- Lancaster, "A Return of the Present State of Capt. John McClughans Company at Lancaster June ye 4th 1758." Docketed: "Return Capn. McClughans Compy Lancaster 4th June 1758", 1758 June 4; Ms, 2 p. (Box Box 4)
- Lancaster, "A Return of the State of Capt. Benjamin Noxon 's Company at Lancaster June ye 4th 1758." Docketed: "Return Captain Noxons Company Lancaster June 4: 1758", 1758 June 4; MsS, 2 p. (Box Box 4)
- Fort Loudoun, William Trent to [Forbes?]. Docketed: "Trent & Bosomworth Ind: Affairs. Carlisle June 7th", 1758 June 5; ALS, 2 p. (Box Box 4)
- Winchester, Bosomworth to Bouquet. Docketed: "Capt. Bossomworth receivd 7th June", 1758 June 5; ALS, 4 p. (Box Box 4)
- Williamsburg, Francis Fauquier to St. Clair. Docketed: (1) "Govr. Fauquier to Sir John St. Clair, " (2) "Governor Fauquier to Sir John St. Clair Williamsburgh June 6th", 1758 June 6; LS, 4 p. (Box Box 4)
- Carlisle, Bouquet to James Burd, Ralph Harding, [William?] Armstrong, John Hambright and John Billings. Beneath the above is their response. Docketed: "Survey on Provisions at Carlisle 6th: June 1758", 1758 June 6; LS, 2 p. (Box Box 4)
- Philadelphia, Forbes to Abercromby. Docketed: "Copy Letter to Genll Abercromby Philad June 7th", 1758 June 7; LS (copy), 4 p. (Box Box 4)
- Philadelphia, Forbes to Bouquet. Docketed: "Copy Letter to Col: Bouquet. Philad: June 8th", [1758] June 8; LS (copy), 3 p. (Box Box 4)
- Conococheague, Sharpe to Forbes. Docketed: "Governour Sharp Conegogce June 9th", 1758 June 9; LS, 3 p. (Box Box 4)
- Conococheague, Sharpe to Forbes. Docketed: "Letter Govr Sharp to Brigdr Gll Forbes Conegocheig June 9th 1758", 1758 June 9; LS, 12 p. (Box Box 4)
- Fort Cumberland, John Dagworthy to Forbes. Docketed: "Capt. Dagworthy Fort Cumberland. June 9th", 1758 June 9; ALS, 2 p. (Box Box 4)
- Winchester, Bosomworth to Bouquet. Docketed: "Capt. Bosomworth Winchester June 9th", 1758 June 9; ALS, 4 p. (Box Box 4)
- Carlisle, Draper S. Wood to Forbes. Docketed: "Commissary Wood Carlisle June 9th", 1758 June 9; ALS, 3 p. (Box Box 4)
- Winchester, St. Clair to Forbes. Docketed: "Sir John St. Clair Winchester June 9th", 1758 June 9; ALS, 2 p. (Box Box 4)
- Aughguago, George Croghan to the officers at Wyoming. Docketed: "Copy Letter of Mr George Croghan to the officers at Wyomink ", 1758 June 10; L (copy), 2 p. (Box Box 4)
- "Extract of a Letter from a Gentleman in London to his Friend in Barbados dated 10 June 1758." Docketed: "Extracts of Letters containing the News from England ", 1758 June 10; L (copy), 3 p. (Box Box 4)
- Aughquaga, Croghan to William Johnson. Docketed: "Copy, Extract of a Letter from Mr. Croghan to Sir Wm. Johnson 11 June 1758", 1758 June 11; L (copy), 2 p. (Box Box 4)
- John Cary. "Sent to Winchester by order of his Excellency Governor Sharpe...", 1758 June 11; MsS, 1 p. (Box Box 4)
- "At a Conference held on the East Side of The Nesscopekun Mountains about 14 or 15 miles from Wyomink Monday June 12th: 1758 between Charles Thomson, & Frederic Post messengers from the Government of Pennsylvania and Teedyuscung, King of the Delawares." Docketed: "Conference King Tediuscung & Mr Thompson June", 1758 June 12; Ms, 3 p. (Box Box 4)
- Pennsylvania. "A proportion of Ordnance and Stores for Pensilvania." Docketed: "Proportion of Stores for Pensilvania June 13th: 1758", 1758 June 13; Ms, 7 p. (Box Box 4)
- Philadelphia, Col. Archibald Montgomery. "Field Return of the 1st Highland Battalion Commanded by the Honble Colo. Archd. Montgomery Camp near Philadelphia June 13th 1758." Docketed: "Field Return of the 1st Highland Battn. Commanded by the Honble Colo. Archd Montgomery Camp near Philadelphia 13th June 1758", 1758 June 13; Ms, 2 p. (Box Box 4)
- George Anderson. "Return of the Officers and Men Military and Civil of the Detachment of the Royal Regiment of Artillery Commanded by Captain Lieutenant Geo: Anderson. June 13th 1758." Docketed: "Return of the Detachment of the Royal Regt of Artillery for Pensilvania June 13 1758", 1758 June 13; MsS, 2 p. (Box Box 4)
- Conococheague, Sharpe to St. Clair. Docketed: "Govr Sharp to Sir John St. Clair Conegogcu June 14th", 1758 June 14; LS, 2 p. (Box Box 4)
- Draper S. Wood and Christopher Kilby. "The allowance of Provisions for one Man Seven Days as agreed by myself & Mr. Joshua Howell head Agent for the Contractors." Docketed: "Comissary Wood & Mr Kilbys Allowance of Provisions June 18", 1758 June 15-18; Ms, 2 p. (Box Box 4)
- Philadelphia, Charles Thomson and Christian Frederick Post to Denny and Forbes. "To the Honourable Willm: Denny Esquire & to the Honourable Brigadier General Forbes. The Report of Chas Thomson & Christian Frederic Post who were sent with Messages to the Indians on Susquehannah June 1758" Docketed: "Indian intelligence Mr Thompson Mr. Post Philad: June 16th", 1758 June 16; MsS, 15 p. (Box Box 4)
- Carlisle, St. Clair to [Forbes]. Docketed: "Sir John St Clair Carlisle June 16th", 1758 June 16; ALS, 4 p. (Box Box 4)
- Philadelphia, Forbes to St. Clair. Docketed: "Copy Letter to Sir J: St Clair Philad: June 16th 1758", 1758 June 16; L (copy), 4 p. (Box Box 4)
- Carlisle, St. Clair to [Forbes]. Docketed: "Sir J St Clair Carlisle June 17th", 1758 June 17; ALS, 2 p. (Box Box 4)
- Carlisle, St. Clair to [Forbes]. Docketed: "Sir John St Clair Carlisle June 17th", 1758 June 17; ALS, 3 p. (Box Box 4)
- Fort Johnson, Sir William Johnson to Abercromby. Docketed: "Extract of a Letter from Sir Wm. Johnson Bart. to Major. Genl. Abercromby dated at Fort Johnson 18 June 1758", 1758 June 18; L (copy), 2 p. (Box Box 4)
- Philadelphia, Forbes to Bouquet. Docketed: "Copy Letter to C: Bouquet Philad: June 19th", [1758] June 19; L (copy), 3 p. (Box Box 4)
- Philadelphia, Frederick Post. "Journal of Frederick Post Journey from Philadelphia to Wayomick June 20th. 1758" Docket: "Copy Journal of Frederick Post 20th June 1758", 1758 June 20-30; MsS (copy), 4 p. (Box Box 4)
- Camp before Louisbourg, Captain Fletcher to Docketed: "Copy Letter of Captain Fletcher of Otways of ye 22d & 29th June from Cabarouse Bay", 1758 June 22-29; L (copy), 3 p. (Box Box 4)
- Fort Loudoun, Upper Cherokees, George Turner to [Forbes?]. Docketed: "Letters Geo. Turner Fort Loudoun 23d June 1758", 1758 June 23; ALS, 3 p. (Box Box 4)
- Fort Loudoun, Upper Cherokees, George Turner to [Forbes?], 1758 June 23; ALS, 4 p. (Box Box 4)
- Winchester, Byrd to [Forbes]. Docketed: "Letter Colo. Byrd Winchester 23d June", 1758 June 23; ALS, 4 p. (Box Box 4)
- Carlisle, St. Clair to Forbes. Docketed: "Sir John St Clair Carlisle June 23d", 1758 June 23; LS, 2 p. (Box Box 4)
- Fort Edward, Abercromby to Forbes. Docketed: "Genll Abercromby Fort Edward June 24 Re July 6th", 1758 June 24; LS, 4 p. (Box Box 4)
- Camp near Philadelphia, Archibald Montgomery. "Return of the First Highland Battalion Commanded by The Honble Colo. Archd. Montgomery Camp near Philadelphia 24th June 1758." Docketed: "Return of the first Highland Battalion Commanded by The Honble Colo. Archd Montgomery camp near Philadelphia 24th June 1758", 1758 June 24; Ms, 2 p. (Box Box 4)
- Raystown, Bosomworth to Forbes. Docketed: "Letter Capt. Bossomworth Raestow [sic] 25th June", 1758 June 25; ALS, 3 p. (Box Box 4)
- Fort Edward. "The Enemy having become Masters of Fort William Henry..." Docketed: "Copy General Order from Majr. Genl. Abercromby declaring the Capitulation of Fort William Henry to be void June 25. 1758", 1758 June 25; Ms (copy), 2 p. (Box Box 4)
- Fort Edward, Abercromby to the Marquis de Vaudreuil. Docketed: "Extract of a Letter from Majr. Genl. Abercromby to Governor Gen'l of Canada June 26. 1758", 1758 June 26; L (copy), 3 p. (Box Box 4)
- "Journal of Moses Tetamy, a messinger sent by the Governor of New Jersey to the Minisink Indians on the head branches of Susquehanagh. " Docketed: "Journal of Moses Titamy ", 1758 June 27 -July 14; Ms, 4 p. (Box Box 4)
- Albany, [George] Appy to Forbes. Docketed: "Mr Appy -- Albany June 27. R July 6th", 1758 June 27; ALS, 2 p. (Box Box 4)
- Philadelphia. "At the State-House on Tuesday the 27th: June 1758." Docketed: "Minutes of the Cherokee's Messages to the Six Nations June 27. 1758. for General Forbes", 1758 June 27; Ms, 4 p. (Box Box 4)
- Jacob Gooding. "A Report of the State of the Company under the command of Jacob Gooding given at Carlisle June 29th 1758 being the day marched from thence for Fort Frederick ", 1758 June 29; MsS, 1 p. (Box Box 4)
- Carlisle and Fort Frederick. Richard Wells. "A Report of Major Well's Company at Carlisle June 29, 1758.... A Report of the above Company at Fort Frederick July 19, 1758", 1758 June 29 -July 19; Ms, 1 p. (Box Box 4)
- Raystown, etc., Edward Ward and Asher Clayton. Journal. Docketed: "Journal of Captain Ward, & Captain Clayton sent to view the Roads", 1758 June 29 -July 3; Ms, 7 p. (Box Box 4)
- Carlisle, St. Clair to Forbes. Docketed: "Letter Sir John St Clair Carlisle June 30th", 1758 June 30; ALS, 3 p. (Box Box 4)
- Fort Johnson, George Croghan to Denny. Docketed: "Copy Letter of George Croghan to Govr Denny 30th June 1758", 1758 June 30; L (copy), 2 p. (Box Box 5)
- Allegheny Hill, Edward Ward to Bouquet, Camp at Raystown, 1758 June 30; ALS, 2 p. (Box Box 5)
- Philadelphia, Denny to [Forbes?] Docketed: "Letter Govr Denny July", 1758 July; LS, 3 p. (Box Box 5)
- Camp at Lake George, Abercromby to Forbes. Docketed: "Gen: Abercromby Lake George. July -- 1758", 1758 July; LS, 8 p. (Box Box 5)
- Carlisle, Adam Hoops. "A Calculation of Provisions to Serve six Thousand Men three Months or 84 days." Docketed: "State of Provisions at Carlisle July 1758", 1758 July; MsS, 2 p. (Box Box 5)
- Carlisle, St. Clair to Forbes. Docketed: "Letter Sir John St Clair Carlisle 1st July", 1758 July 1; LS, 2 p. (Box Box 5)
- Winchester, Christopher Gist to St. Clair. Docketed: "Letter to Sir John St Clair from Mr. Gist Winchester July 1st", 1758 July 1; LS, 3 p. (Box Box 5)
- Camp before Louisbourg, Capt. [Alexander] Mackintosh to [Forbes]. Docketed: "Letter Capt. Mc. Intosh Camp before Louisbourg 2 July 1758", 1758 July 2; ALS, 4 p. (Box Box 5)
- Carlisle, Draper S. Wood to Forbes. "A Return of Provisions in store at Carlyle belonging to the Contractors July the 5th 1758." Docketed: "Return of Provisions in store at Carlisle 5th July 1758", 1758 July 5; Ms, 2 p. (Box Box 5)
  Enclosure: "The Nearest Computation..." 1 p.
- "Minutes of Conferences between The Honourable William Denny Esquire Governor of Pennssylvania and Teedyuscung King of the Delaware Indians July 1758." Docketed: "Minutes of a Conference between Govr. Denny & Teedyuscung July 1758", 1758 July 6-15; Ms, 15 p. (Box Box 5)
  Includes petition, 1758 July 12, "To William Denny... The Memorial of the Freemen..."
- Philadelphia. "The Governor being informed, that Teedyuscung and Fifty Indians.... At a Conference held at the State House Friday the 7th: July 1758...." Docketed: "Copy Conferences betwn. Governor of Pennsylvania & Teedyuscung in July 1758", 1758 July 6-12; Ms (copy), 14 p. (Box Box 5)
- Camp near Raystown. "Instructions for Capts: Ward & Clayton" Docket: "Capts: Ward & Clayton's Instructions", 1758 July 7; Ms, 4 p. (Box Box 5)
- Camp at Carlisle, Forbes to Abercromby. Docketed: "Copy letter to Genll. Abercromby: Camp at Carlisle July 10th", 1758 July 7-10; LS (copy, partially in Forbe's hand), 7 p. (Box Box 5)
- Headquarters at Carlisle, Forbes to Governors Denny, Sharpe, Fauquier, Dobbs, Lyttleton, and Ellis. Docketed: "Copy Circular letter to the Southern provinces Carlisle July 8th 1758", 1758 July 8; LS (draft), 2 p. (Box Box 5)
- "List of Officers & Soldiers, Kill'd & Wounded at the Attack of Ticonderoga the 8th. July 1758", 1758 July 8; Ms, 2 p. (Box Box 5)
- Carlisle, Draper S. Wood to Forbes. "A Calculation of Provisions to serve six Thousand Men three months or 84 days." Docketed: "Calculation of provisions for 6000 men", 1758 July 8; Ms, 2 p. (Box Box 5)
- "Return of the Names of the Officers of the Several Regiments who were killed or Wounded near Ticonderoga July 8th 1758." Docket: "List of Officers Killed and Wounded", 1758 July 8; Ms, 2 p. (Box Box 5)
- "Return of Killed, Missing & Wounded of His Majestys Troops & Provincials in the action near Ticonderoga July 8th 1758." Docketed: "Return of the Killed of His Majestys Troops and Provincials near Ticonderoga. July 8th. 1758", 1758 July 8; Ms, 2 p. (Box Oversize)
- Albany, Richard Huck to Forbes. Docketed: "Dr Huck Albany July 9th", 1758 July 9; ALS, 4 p. (Box Box 5)
- Camp at Fort Cumberland, Byrd to [Forbes.] Docketed: "Letter Colo. Byrd Fort Cumberland July 9th 1758", 1758 July 9; ALS, 2 p. (Box Box 5)
- Burlington, Francis Bernard to Denny, containing "Resolve of the Jersey Assembly." Docketed: "Indians Copy Extract of Governor Bernard's Letter to Govr Denny & Resolve of Jersey Assembly", 1758 July 10; L (copy), 2 p. (Box Box 5)
- Louisbourg, Arthur Morris. "State of the Grenadr: Company of the 17th: Regiment, Camp before Louisbourg 10th: July 1758" Docketed: "State of the Grenadr: Company of the 17th: Regiment of Foot ", 1758 July 10; MsS, 2 p. (Box Box 5)
- Camp at Raystown, Bosomworth. "A Return of the Indian stores at the Camp at Rays Town" Docketed: "A Return of the Indian Stores at the Camp at Rays Town July 12th 1758", 1758 July 13; MsS, 3 p. (Box Box 5)
- Camp at Raystown, Bosomworth. "A List of Goods wanting to equip three Hundred more Indians expected to join for the Service of the Expedition" Docketed: "List of Indian Goods wanting at Rays Town 13th. July 1758", 1758 July 13; MsS, 2 p. (Box Box 5)
- Gen. Wolfe's Camp near the Grand Battery, Arthur Morris to Forbes, Philadelphia. Docketed: "Letter Colo. Morris Genl. Wolfes Camp near the Grand Battery 14 July 1758", 1758 July 14; ALS, 4 p. (Box Box 5)
- Carlisle, Draper S. Wood to Forbes. "A Return of Stores belonging to the Crown at Carlisle July ye. 14th 1758" Docket: "Return of stores at Carlisle July 14th", 1758 July 14; MsS, 2 p. (Box Box 5)
- Carlisle, Draper S. Wood to Forbes. "A Return of Provisions in Store at Carlisle belonging to the Contractors July 14th 1758", 1758 July 14; MsS, 1 p. (Box Box 5)
- Raystown. "A Return of Provisions at Rays Town on the Road thither, & other places; now ready July 14th. 1758." Docketed: "Calculation of provisions--The within calculation is exclusive of what provision is Laid on at Fort Frederick and Fort Cumberland ", 1758 July 14; Ms, 2 p. (Box Box 5)
- Ft. Hunter, John Montgomery to Lieutenant Finley, 1758 July 14; MsS, 1 p. (Box Box 5)
  Concerns imprisonment of deserters.
- Camp at Lake George, to Richard Peters. Docketed: "Copy Letter to Richard Peters from an Officer of good sense who was at Ticonderogo during the unhappy attack", 1758 July 14; L (copy), 4 p. (Box Box 5)
  A manuscript map of Fort Ticonderoga and the surrounding country is enclosed.
- Philadelphia, Richard Peters. "By the Honourable William Denny..." Docketed: "Copy 15 July 1758 Governor Denny's Pass to Mr. Frederick Post and the Indians of his Company", 1758 July 15; MsS (copy), 2 p. (Box Box 5)
- Philadelphia, Richard Peters. "By the Honourable William Denny Esquire Lieutenant Governor and Commander in Chief of the Province of Pennsylvania... To Mr Frederick Post Greeting." Docketed: "Copy. 15th July 1758 Commission to Mr Frederick Post ", 1758 July 15; MsS (copy), 2 p. (Box Box 5)
- Philadelphia, Denny to Christian Frederick Post. Docket: "Copy. Instructions to Mr Frederick Post 15 July 1758", 1758 July 15; L (copy), 3 p. (Box Box 5)
- Archibald Kennedy to Andrew Elliot. Docketed: "Copy Letter Archd. Kennedy Esqr. to Mr Elliot. 15 July 1758", 1758 July 15; L (copy), 2 p. (Box Box 5)
- Camp at Fort Cumberland, Bosomworth to Forbes. Docketed: "Letter Capt. Bossomworth Fort Cumberland 15th July 1758", 1758 July 15; ALS, 3 p. (Box Box 5)
- Christian Frederick Post. "A Daily Journal kept by Frederick Post Commencing July 15th. 1758", 1758 July 15 -September 20; Ms, 57 p. (Box Box 5)
- Philadelphia, Peters to Forbes. Docketed: "Mr Peters July 16th", 1758 July 16; LS, 3 p. (Box Box 5)
- Albany, W. Forbes to Forbes, Philadelphia. Docketed: "Letter Capt. Forbes Albany 16th July 1758", 1758 July 16; ALS, 7 p. (Box Box 5)
- Philadelphia, Peters to [Forbes]. Docketed: "Letter Mr. Peters Philadelphia 17th July 1758", 1758 July 17; ALS, 3 p. (Box Box 5)
- St. Christophers, Wal Pringle to [Forbes.] Docketed: "Letter Mr. Pringle St Christophers 17th July 1758", 1758 July 17; ALS, 2 p. (Box Box 5)
- New York, Hugh Wallace to Forbes. Docketed: "Letter Mr. Wallace N: York 17th July 1758", 1758 July 17; ALS, 4 p. (Box Box 5)
- New York, Gilbert McAdam to Forbes. Docketed: "Letter Mr. McAdam New York 17th July 1758", 1758 July 17; ALS, 2 p. (Box Box 5)
- Greenwich, McAdam to [Forbes]. Docketed: "Letter Mr. McAdam Greenwich 17th July 1758", 1758 July 17; ALS, 4 p. (Box Box 5)
- New York, William Smith, Jr. to. Docketed: "Copy letter of Mr. Wm. Smith Junior of New York", 1758 July 17; L (copy), 2 p. (Box Box 5)
- New York, Archibald Kennedy to Denny. Docketed: "Copy Letter to Govr. Denny from Mr. Kennedy N. York 17th July 1758", 1758 July 17; L (copy), 2 p. (Box Box 5)
- Carlisle, Francis Halkett. "A Sketch of the number of Troops under Brigadier General Forbes's Command Carlisle 17th July 1758." Docketed: "Sketch of the number of Troops under Brigadier Forbes's Command Carlisle 17 July 1758", 1758 July 17; MsS, 2 p. (Box Box 5)
- New York, John Watts to Richard Pe-ters. Docketed: "Copy Letter of Mr. Watts of New York", 1758 July 17; L (copy), 2 p. (Box Box 5)
- New York, Alexander Colden to. Docketed: "Extract of Letter from Mr. Alexander Colden ", 1758 July 17; L (copy), 2 p. (Box Box 5)
- Camp at Carlisle, Forbes to Abercromby. Docketed: "Copy Letter to Gll Abercrombie Carlisle Camp July 18th 1758", 1758 July 18; L (copy), 3 p. (Box Box 5)
- Philadelphia, Peters to [Forbes] Docketed: "Mr Peters July 18th", 1758 July 18; ALS, 3 p. (Box Box 5)
- Philadelphia, James Coultas to Forbes, Carlisle. Docketed: "Mr Coultas Philadelp. July 18", 1758 July 18; LS, 3 p. (Box Box 5)
- Philadelphia, Denny to Forbes. Docketed: "Letter Governr. Denny Philada. 19th July 1758", 1758 July 19; LS, 2 p. (Box Box 5)
- Fort Loudoun, Lewis Ourry to Forbes. Docketed: "Letter Mr. Ourry Fort Loudoun 19th July 1758", 1758 July 19; LS, 2 p. (Box Box 5)
- Carlisle, Richard Dudgeon, Report on the fort at Carlisle. Docketed: "Report of the State of Car-lisle Fort", 1758 July 19; MsS, 3 p. (Box Box 5)
- Philadelphia, [Israel] Pemberton to Forbes. Docketed: "Letter Mr. Pemberton Philada. 19th July 1758", 1758 July 19; ALS, 3 p. (Box Box 5)
- Williamsburg, Francis Fauquier to Forbes. Docketed: "Letter Governr. Faquier Williamsburgh 20th July 1758", 1758 July 20; ALS, 3 p. (Box Box 5)
- Camp at Raystown, Bosomworth to Forbes. Docketed: "Letter Capt. Bossomworth Raestown 21st July 1758", 1758 July 20; ALS, 4 p. (Box Box 5)
- Raystown, Bosomworth, "The Yellow Birds party consisting of fourteen Cherokee Indians and two white Men went from this Camp...within two Miles of the French Fort...." Docketed: "Indian intelligence Camp at Rays Town 20th July 1758", 1758 July 20; MsS, 4 p. (Box Box 5)
- Raystown, Edward Biddle. "King's Stores, Camp near Raystown." Docketed: "Kings Stores Raystown 20th July 1758", 1758 July 20; Ms, 2 p. (Box Box 5)
- Camp at Carlisle, Forbes to Sharpe. Docketed: "Copy Letter Govr. Sharp Camp at Carlisle July 20th 1758", 1758 July 20; L (copy), 3 p. (Box Box 5)